paymoapp.com 2019-10-29

# Paymo Privacy Policy

This privacy policy ("Policy") discloses the privacy practices for any websites or software Services (including any applications developed for iPhone, Android, Mac, Windows or Linux) owned by Paymo. Each of the websites and/or services covered by this Policy are referred to as a "site" or "sites". 

Your privacy is extremely important to us and we're committed to protect it. Any questions you might have about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to our Data Protection Officer at dpo@paymoapp.com.

1. By using Paymo, you agree to the collection and use of your data ("Personal Data") and your customers data ("Customer Data"). 

**Personal Data**   
Such data may include things such as your name, username, password, email address, business information, as well as relevant demographic information. In addition we may automatically collect information about your computer, device or internet access, such as IP address, web browser, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, and your usage of our sites and applications.

**Customer Data**   
You may submit various types of data into the Sites for storing & processing Customer Data. Customer Data may include, without limitation, personal information such as names, email addresses and phone numbers of your customers, potential customers and other users of and visitors to your websites, or any other properties (“People”). We will only use, disclose and otherwise process Customer Data for the purposes set forth in your agreement with us.

**How we use the data we collect**

  * To provide & maintain our products and services
  * To process your customer support inquiries and deliver customer service
  * To process your payments
  * To control unauthorised use or abuse or detect, investigate and prevent activities that are unlawful or that violate our policies
  * To monitor usage or the service
  * To communicate directly with you, including by sending you newsletters, promotions and special offers or information about new products and services. 

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**

We share your data strictly with sub-processors/companies that allow us to operate the service, as follows:

_Data Hosting_   
Amazon Web Services, Inc. 

_Customer Support_   
Intercom R&D Unlimited Company 

_Payment Information_   
Any credit card information you provide as part of your Payment Information is collected and processed directly by our payment processor PayPal (Europe) S.a.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. We never receive or store your full credit card By using Paymo, you agree to the collection and use of your data. PayPal commits to complying with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) and using industry standard security. 

2. We will never sell or rent any information with any third parties.

3. Data Ownership   
You always retain ownership rights you may have in any content, data you upload or otherwise provide to us through the sites (the "user content").   
We provide an open [API](http://github.com/paymoapp/api) that gives you access to all data stored in Paymo. We limit the access to personal data to those needing to act out the processing (our technical support team). 

4. You have the Right to be Forgotten. You can delete all data related to your account at any time.

5. We don't tolerate spam. We will send out emails to customers only in the case of service related announcements.

6. Paymo uses "cookies" to store session information, and thus will set and access cookies on your computer(s).

7. EU individuals have rights to access personal information about them, to limit use and disclosure of their personal information, and to ensure that such personal information is accurate and relevant for the purposes for which it is collected. Paymo is committed to respect these rights (Right to Access, Right to be Forgotten & Data Portability).   
In case of a security breach all affected customers will be notified by email and directly in the app within 72 hours of first having become aware of the breach. Paymo designs and develops all systems with Privacy in mind and follows best practices such as data minimisation and limiting the access to personal data to those needing to act out the processing (our technical support team).  

8. This website uses the Google AdWords Remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Paymo website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [ Google Ad Preferences page](https://adssettings.google.com/), and if you want to you can [ opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings ](https://adssettings.google.com/) or [permanently using a browser plugin.](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/iba-opt-out-by-google/gbiekjoijknlhijdjbaadobpkdhmoebb)

Last updated on May 18th, 2018
